因为实际在发生的，以及我们今天所知的，
because what actually happened, and what we know today,
有不同的人写了这些，
and there's different people writing about this,
这是英格兰银行的数据，
this data here is from the Bank of England,
数据显示从 1970 年代开始 和 80 年代后
is that lots of what finance was actually doing
银行业实际一直在做的事情
from the 1970s and '80s on
基本上就是给自己融资：
was basically financing itself:
金融融资资金。
finance financing finance.
我的意思是金融，保险和房地产。
And what I mean by that is finance, insurance and real estate.
事实上，在英国
In fact, in the UK,
大概 10% - 20% 的融资
something like between 10 and 20 percent of finance
能够最终流向实体经济， 流向行业，
finds its way into the real economy, into industry,
比如能源部门，制药行业，
say, into the energy sector, into pharmaceuticals,
IT 部门，
into the IT sector,